in a previous lesson we went over how
在上一课中，我们复习了如何
you can use the various Tools in
您可以使用中的各种工具
inkscape to draw straight lines and
Inkscape绘制直线和
curved lines but what if you have a line
曲线，但如果你有一条线呢？
that's already drawn and you just want
已经画好了，你只想
to smooth it out like you see here
就像你在这里看到的那样，让它变得平稳
that's what we'll be addressing in
这就是我们将在
today's tutorial so let's get started so
今天的教程，让我们开始吧
for this demonstration I'm just going to
在这个演示中，我只想
draw a quick and sloppy line using the
绘制一条快速且松散的线条
freehand lines tool which is located
所在位置的手绘线工具
over here in the toolbar or you can
在这里的工具栏中，或者您可以
access it by pressing the letter P on
通过按字母P来访问它
your keyboard
您的键盘
I'm going to come up here to the
我要到这里来
smoothing setting and bring that all the
平滑的设置，并将所有
way down to zero and then I'm going to
降到零，然后我要
click and drag on my canvas to draw a
在我的画布上单击并拖动以绘制
really rough sloppy line like that
真的很粗糙，很草率，像这样
now if I go to the nodes tool you can
现在，如果我转到节点工具，您可以
see over here there's a lot going on in
看这里有很多东西在里面
the way of nodes
结点之路
and you can see here we have a little
你可以看到这里我们有一些
bit of a uh like a hard corner right
有点，呃，就像一个硬角，对吧
there that's okay though because we can
不过，这没问题，因为我们可以
salvage this path let's go to the pathfx
抢救这条小路吧，我们去探路吧
menu by going to path and selecting
菜单，方法是转到路径并选择
pathfx
路径FX
from the pathfx menu click the plus icon
从pathfx菜单中单击加号图标
down here in the bottom left corner to
在这里的左下角到
add a new path effect
添加新的路径效果
the path effect we're looking for is
我们正在寻找的路径效应是
called simplify so scroll through your
名为SIMPLIZE，因此可以在您的
list here and look for simplify or you
请在此处列出并查找Simply or You
can type it into the search bar up here
我可以在上面的搜索栏中输入它
I'm going to click on this checkbox
我要点击这个复选框
right here to add this path effect and
在这里添加此路径效果和
once that's added all you have to do is
添加后，您所要做的就是
come down here to where it says roughly
到这里来，它大致上写着
threshold and increase that value so I'm
阈值并增加该值，所以我
going to hold a click over this plus
在这个加号上点击一下
icon here and depending on how rough
图标在此处，具体取决于粗糙程度
your path is you may have to use a
您的方法是，您可能必须使用
higher value so I'm going to hold a
更高的价值，所以我将持有
click over this for a while and if you
点击这里一段时间，如果您
notice as I do that it is slowly but
请注意，当我这样做时，它是缓慢的，但
surely becoming a smoother path
肯定会成为一条更平坦的道路
now if I want to increase it increase
现在，如果我想增加它，增加
this even more I can come over here to
这更是我可以来这里的原因
where it says steps and start increasing
上面写着步数并开始增加
that as well until I get an even
在我拿到平局之前也是如此
smoother path
更顺畅的道路
so every path will be different but
所以每条路都是不同的，但
based on your drawing you may have to
根据您的图画，您可能需要
use a higher or lower value here so I'm
在此使用较高或较低的值，因此我
going to cycle through the options and
我将循环浏览这些选项和
see what looks best I think 10 looks
看看什么看起来最好我认为10个看起来
good right about there and this value
好的，就在那里，这个值
looks good as well so I'm going to leave
看起来也不错，所以我要走了
this just as it is
事情就是这样的
so as you can see we now have a much
如你所见，我们现在有很多
smoother path and this is a temporary
更平坦的道路，这是一个暂时的
effect if I come up here to where it
如果我走到这里的话会有影响
says simplify I can toggle the
说SIMPLE我可以切换
visibility of this off and on to get
断断续续的可见性以获得
back to my original path
回到我最初的道路
if I want to finalize this effect I can
如果我想最终确定这个效果，我可以
come up here to where it says path and
走到上面写着路径的地方
go to object to path now if you notice
如果您注意到了，请立即转到对象到路径
here although the line is a lot smoother
虽然在这里排队要顺畅得多
it's not quite perfect there's a little
这不是很完美，有一点
bit of hard Corners in here but that's
在这里有一些困难的角落，但那是
okay because we can iron those out
好的，因为我们可以解决这些问题
manually let's come over here to the
手动操作，让我们来到这里
edit pads by nodes tool and if you
按节点编辑焊盘工具，如果您
notice if you click on this node right
请注意，如果您右击此节点
here where we have a corner we have
在这里，我们有一个角落，我们有
these two handles coming off the sides
这两个把手从两边掉下来
of it in order for this path in order
为了让这条路井然有序
for this node to be smooth we need these
为了使该节点流畅，我们需要这些
handles to be running parallel with each
句柄应与每个句柄并行运行
other so I'm going to move these handles
其他的，所以我要移动这些手柄
so that they're parallel with each other
所以它们是平行的
and we have a smooth path here a quicker
我们这里有一条平坦的路，更快
way to do that would be to just hold
要做到这一点，方法就是按住
Ctrl and click on the Node and it'll
按住Ctrl键并单击该节点，它将
make them automatically smooth like that
让它们自动变得像那样光滑
and then you can just move the handles
然后你只需移动手柄
around like that to adjust it as needed
就像这样，根据需要进行调整
I'll come over here and do the same
我会来到这里，做同样的事情
thing I'll hold Ctrl and click on the
我要按住Ctrl键并单击
Node
节点
and again you can click on the Node
同样，您可以单击该节点
again and adjust the handles as needed
再次并根据需要调整手柄
and I'll just go through here and adjust
我只需要穿过这里，调整一下
all of these nodes to ensure that they
所有这些节点以确保它们
are all smooth and they all look the way
都很流畅，看起来都很顺畅
I want them to look
我想让他们看看
and as I do so I will adjust the handle
当我这样做时，我会调整手柄
so I have the right Contour that I
所以我有正确的轮廓
prefer
更喜欢
now we have smoothed out that path so
现在我们已经铺平了这条道路，
that's how you can smooth out a rough
这就是如何抚平粗糙的
path using inkscape if you found this
如果您发现此，使用inkscape路径
lesson useful then consider checking out
课程有用，然后考虑查看
my inkscape master class it's a
我的水墨风景大师班是一堂
collection of over 60 videos where I go
收集了我去过的60多个视频
over all of the tools and features in
中的所有工具和功能
inkscape and I explain what they are and
inkscape和我解释了它们是什么，
demonstrate how they work kind of like
演示它们的工作原理有点像
how I did in this video we even have a
我在这个视频中的表现我们甚至有一个
private Community where you can ask
私人社区，您可以询问
questions and get help from me anytime
随时向我提问并寻求帮助
you want and best of all there's no
你想要的，最重要的是没有
monthly membership fees you just pay 17
每月只需支付17美元会员费
one time and you're in for Life I'll
一次，你就会终身监禁我会
have some information about that down
有一些相关信息
below if you want to check that out as
如果您想检查一下，请在下面作为
always thanks for watching
始终感谢观看
foreign
外国